Guide to the Colgate University class records A1012
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
Colgate University class records
1867-2007
A1012
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
10 cubic feet
Access to Collection
Collection is open for research.
Colgate University--Alumni and alumnae.; Colgate University--Students.; Correspondence.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; Reunions.; Universities and colleges--History--19th century.; Universities and colleges--History--20th century.
- Class of 1836, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Class of 1856, 1901-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Class of 1862, 1867-1882 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Class of 1863, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Class of 1882 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Class of 1884, 1909-1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Class of 1885 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Class of 1886, 1886-1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Class of 1887, 1887-1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Class of 1888, 1888-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Class of 1889 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Class of 1890, 1890-1894 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Class of 1891, 1889-1936 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Class of 1892, 1892, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893, 1893-1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Class of 1894, 1892-1909 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Class of 1895, 1895-1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Class of 1896, 1892-1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Class of 1897, 1897, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Class of 1898, 1898-1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Class of 1898 - correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Class of 1898 - correspondence and postcards, 1944-1949, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Class of 1899, 1899-1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Class of 1900, 1900-1940 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Class of 1901, 1899-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Class of 1901, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Class of 1901, 1942-1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Class of 1901, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Class of 1901, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Class of 1902, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Class of 1902 scrapbook, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Class of 1902, 1902-1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Class of 1902 correspondence, 1926-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Class of 1902 correspondence, 1946-1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Class of 1902 correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Class of 1902 correspondence, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Class of 1903, 1903-1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Class of 1903, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Class of 1903 correspondence, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Class of 1904, 1904-1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Class of 1905, 1905-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Class of 1905 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Class of 1905, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Class of 1905 anniversary gift fund, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Class of 1905 correspondence, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Class of 1905 reunion, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Class of 1905 twenty-fifth anniversary, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Class of 1906 publications, 1906-1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Class of 1906, 1904-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Class of 1906, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Class of 1906, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Class of 1906 correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Class of 1906 - Quarta Centennial directory, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Class of 1906 - 65th Reunion, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Class of 1907 correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Class of 1907 - published letters, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Class of 1907, 1932-1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Class of 1907 - 65th Reunion, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Class of 1908, 1908-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Class of 1908 correspondence, including 60th reunion, 1963-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Class of 1908 - 65th Reunion, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Class of 1909, 1909-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Class of 1909 anniversary gift fund, 1949-1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Class of 1909 correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Class of 1909 - 65th Reunion, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Class of 1910 - 25th Reunion Binder, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Class of 1910, 1909-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Class of 1910, 1950-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Class of 1910 - biographical history, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Class of 1910 - biographical history, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Class of 1910 - biographical history, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Class of 1910 anniversary gift fund, 1951-1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Class of 1910 - 60th Reunion, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Class of 1910 correspondence, 1965-1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Class of 1911, 1911-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Class of 1911 correspondence, 1965-1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Class of 1911 - 60th Reunion, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Class of 1911 - 65th Reunion, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Class of 1912 correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Class of 1912 - 60th Reunion, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Class of 1912, 1912-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Class of 1913, 1913-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Class of 1913 correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Class of 1913 anniversary gift fund, 1952-1964 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Class of 1913 - 55th Reunion, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Class of 1913 - 60th Reunion, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Class of 1914 newsletter, 1958-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Class of 1914, 1914-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Class of 1914 correspondence, 1964-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Class of 1914 anniversary gift fund, 1955-1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Class of 1914 - 60th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Class of 1914 - 65th Reunion, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Class of 1915, 1915-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Class of 1915 papers from Bliss Youker, 1940-1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Class of 1915 correspondence, 1963-1987 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Class of 1915 anniversary gift fund, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Class of 1915 55th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Class of 1915 - 60th Reunion, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Class of 1915 - 65th Reunion, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Class of 1916, 1916-1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Class of 1916, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Class of 1916 correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Class of 1916 anniversary gift fund, 1951-1966 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Class of 1916 - 55th Reunion, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Class of 1916 - 60th Reunion, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Class of 1916 - 1982 Reunion (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Class of 1917 correspondence, 1964-1982 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Class of 1917 - correspondence, 30th Reunion, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Class of 1917 - correspondence, 35th Reunion, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Class of 1917 - "Thirty-Five Years Later", 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Class of 1917 - "Remember the Time", 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Class of 1917 - 25 and 50 Years later, 1942, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Class of 1917, 1915-1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Class of 1917 - 40th Reunion, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Class of 1917 - 44th Reunion, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Class of 1917 - 50th Reunion, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Class of 1917 - 55th Reunion, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Class of 1917 - 60th Reunion, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Class of 1917 - 65th Reunion, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Class of 1917 anniversary gift fund, 1952-1967 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Class of 1918, 1918-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Class of 1918 correspondence, 1965-1979 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Class of 1918 - From H. Hastings Reddall, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Class of 1918 - 50th Reunion, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Class of 1918 - 50th Reunion Binder, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Class of 1918 - 55th Reunion, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Class of 1918 - 55th Reunion, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Class of 1918 - 55th Reunion, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Class of 1918 - 1977 Reunion, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Class of 1918 - 60th Reunion, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Class of 1918 - 60th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Class of 1918 - 65th reunion, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Class of 1918 Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1968-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Class of 1919, 1915-1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Class of 1919, 1964-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Class of 1919 correspondence, 1964-1983 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Class of 1919 - 55th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Class of 1919 - 60th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Class of 1919 - 65th Reunion, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Class of 1919 - 70th Reunion, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Class of 1920, 1920-1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Class of 1920 correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Class of 1920 - 50th Reunion, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Class of 1920 - 55th Reunion, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Class of 1920 - 60th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Class of 1920 - 1986 Reunion (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Class of 1920 - 70th Reunion, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Class of 1920 - 75th Reunion, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Class of 1921, 1916-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Class of 1921 correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Class of 1921 - 20th Reunion, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Class of 1921 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Class of 1921 - 55th Reunion, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Class of 1921 - 60th Reunion, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Class of 1921 - 65th Reunion, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Class of 1921 - 70th Reunion, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Class of 1922, 1922-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Class of 1922 correspondence, 1952-1972 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Class of 1922 - 50th Reunion, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Class of 1922 - 55th Reunion, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Class of 1922 - 60th Reunion, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Class of 1922 - 65th Reunion, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Class of 1922 - 70th Reunion, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Class of 1923, 1953-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Class of 1923, 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Class of 1923 - correspondence, 1965-1978 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Class of 1923 - 50th Reunion, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Class of 1923 - 55th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Class of 1923 - 60th Reunion, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Class of 1923 - 65th Reunion, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Class of 1923 - 70th Reunion, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Class of 1924, 1924-1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Class of 1924 correspondence and commencement program, 1924-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Class of 1924 - 45th Reunion, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Class of 1924 - 50th Reunion, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Class of 1924 - 55th Reunion binder, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Class of 1924 - 55th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Class of 1924 - 60th Reunion, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Class of 1924 - 65th Reunion, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Class of 1925, 1922-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Class of 1925 correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Class of 1925 - 45th Reunion, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Class of 1925 - 50th reunion, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Class of 1925 - 55th Reunion, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Class of 1925 - 60th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Class of 1925 - 65th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Class of 1925 - 70th Reunion, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Class of 1926, 1931-1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Class of 1926, 1951-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Class of 1926 - Material sent by Bob Head ('26), 1984 July (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Class of 1926 correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Class of 1926 - 45th Reunion, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Class of 1926 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Class of 1926 - 55th Reunion, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Class of 1926 - 60th Reunion, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Class of 1926 - 65th Reunion, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Class of 1926 - 70th Reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Class of 1926 - 75th Reunion, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Class of 1926 - Class of 1931, undated (Box 6)
- Class of 1927, 1952-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Class of 1927 correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Class of 1927 - 45th Reunion, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Class of 1927 - 50th Reunion, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Class of 1927 - 55th Reunion, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Class of 1927 - 60th Reunion, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Class of 1927 - 65th Reunion, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Class of 1927 - 70th and 75 Reunions, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Class of 1928, 1938-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Class of 1928 correspondence, 1962-1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Class of 1928 - 40th and 45th Reunions, 1967-1968, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Class of 1928 - 50th Reunion, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Class of 1928 - 55th and 60th Reunions, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Class of 1928 - 65th Reunion, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Class of 1928 - 75th Reunion, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Class of 1929, 1934-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Class of 1929 pictures, 1939-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Class of 1929, 1962 February - 1969 December (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Class of 1929, 1970 March - 1975 August (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Class of 1929, 1975 October- 1977 September (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Class of 1929, 1977 December - 1980 October (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Class of 1929 newsletters, 1962-1972 (Box 6, Volume 9A)
- Class of 1929 newsletters, 1963-1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Class of 1929 newsletters, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Volume 9B)
- Class of 1929 newsletters, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Class of 1929 newsletters, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Volume 9C)
- Class of 1929 - 45th Reunion, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Class of 1929 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Class of 1929 - 55th, 60th, and 65th Reunions, 1983-1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Class of 1929 - 70th and 75th Reunions, 1998-1999, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Class of 1930, 1930, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Class of 1930 pictures, 1926-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Class of 1930 papers, 1955-1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Class of 1930 papers, 1935-1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Class of 1930 papers, 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Class of 1930 papers, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Class of 1930 correspondence, 1965-1978, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Class of 1930 - 40th and 45th Reunions, 1970, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Class of 1930 - 50th Reunion, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Class of 1930 - 55th and 60th Reunions, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Class of 1930 - 65th, 70th, and 75th Reunions, 1995-2005 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Class of 1931, 1936-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Class of 1931, 1931-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Class of 1931 correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Class of 1931 - 40th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Class of 1931 - 45th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Class of 1931 - 50th Reunion, 1973-1981 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- 1931 is No. 1 in 81!, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Class of 1931 - 55th, 60th, and 65th Reunions, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Class of 1931 - 70th and 75th Reunions, 2000-2006 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Class of 1932, 1932-1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Class of 1932 correspondence, 1962-2000 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Class of 1932 - 35th Reunion, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Class of 1932 - 40th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Class of 1932 - 45th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Class of 1932 - Special Reunion, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Class of 1932 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Class of 1932 - 50th Reunion Book, 1982 (Box 9, Volume 58)
- Class of 1932 - 50th Reunion Book, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Class of 1932 - 50th Reunion Book, 1982 (Box 7, Volume 22)
- Class of 1932 - 55th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Class of 1932 - 60th and 65th Reunions, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Class of 1932 - 70th and 75th Reunions correspondence and photographs, 2001-2007 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Class of 1933, 1933-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Class of 1933 correspondence, 1963-1996 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Class of 1933 - 45th Reunion, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Class of 1933 - 50th Reunion, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Class of 1933 - 50th Reunion Book, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Class of 1933 - 50th Reunion photograph, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Class of 1933 - 55th and 60th Reunions, 1988, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Class of 1933 - 65th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Class of 1933 - 70th and 75th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 2003, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Class of 1934, 1934-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Class of 1934 correspondence, 1964-1996 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Class of 1934 - 35th and 40th Reunions correspondence and photograph, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Class of 1934 - 45th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Class of 1934 - 50th Reunion, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Class of 1934 - 50th Reunion photograph, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Class of 1934 - "50th Reunion Anthology", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Class of 1934 - "50th Reunion Anthology", 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Class of 1934 - "50th Reunion Project", 1977-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Class of 1934 - 55th and 60th Reunions, 1984, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Class of 1934 - 65th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Class of 1934 - 70th Reunion, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Class of 1935, 1935-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Class of 1935 - "Golden Anniversary Class Book", 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Class of 1935 - Commencement booklet (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Class of 1935 correspondence, 1964-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Class of 1935 - 30th and 35th Reunions, 1966, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Class of 1935 - 40th and 45th Reunions correspondence and photograph, 1975, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Class of 1935 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Class of 1935 - 55th Reunion, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Class of 1935 - 60th Reunion and photograph, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Class of 1935 - 65th Reunion, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Class of 1935 - 70th Reunion, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Class of 1936 correspondence, 1969-1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Class of 1936 - 30th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Class of 1936 - 35th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Class of 1936 - 40th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Class of 1936 - 45th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Class of 1936 - 50th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Class of 1936 - 55th Reunion, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Class of 1936 - 60th Reunion, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Class of 1936 - 65th Reunion correspondence and photographs, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Class of 1936 - 70th Reunion correspondence and photograph, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Class of 1936 - Portrait photographs, 1936, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Class of 1936 - "'36 Anthology", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Class of 1936 - 50th Reunion Book, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Class of 1937, 1937-1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Class of 1937 - 70th Reunion, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Class of 1938, 1963, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Class of 1938 - Portrait photographs (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Class of 1939 - 50th Reunion Book, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Class of 1939 - 50th Reunion Book, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Class of 1939 - 50th Reunion Book, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Class of 1939 - 55th Reunion Book, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Class of 1939, 1939-1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Study on Future Success of Graduates, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Class of 1939 - Letters from Faculty, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Class of 1939 - Portrait photos, 1939, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Class of 1940, 1940, 1965, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Class of 1942, 1961-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Class of 1941 - 50th Reunion Book, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Class of 1941- 50th Reunion Material, 1981, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2A)
- Class of 1942 - Fall Freshmen, portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Class of 1942 - Summer Freshmen, portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Class of 1942 - portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Class of 1942 - Fiftieth Reunion Yearbook, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Class of 1943, 1954-2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Class of 1943 - portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 10)
- World War II Memoirs - Colgate University Class of 1943, 2007 (Box 7, Volume 29)
- Photos - Perennials Dinners, 1972, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Class of 1944, 1943-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Class of 1944 - portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Class of 1945, 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Class of 1945 - portrait photos (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Class of 1946, 1942, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Class of 1947, 1945-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Class of 1947 - June 27, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Class of 1948, 1944-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Class of 1948 - 50th Reunion, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Class of 1949, 1953-1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Class of 1950 - Class of 1980 and other earlier years, undated (Box 7)
- Class of 1950, 1950-1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Class of 1951, 1951-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2B)
- Class of 1952, 1952-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3A)
- Class of 1955, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Class of 1956 - photographs, 1956-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3B)
- Class of 1956 - newsletters, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 3C)
- Class of 1957, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Class of 1957- 25th Anniversary Gift Endowment, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Class of 1958, 1958-1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Class of 1959, 1955-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Class of 1960, 1955-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8A)
- Class of 1961, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8B)
- Class of 1962, 1962-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Class of 1964, 1964-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Class of 1965, 1965-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Class of 1967, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Class of 1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Class of 1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Class of 1970 - 25th Reunion Book, 1995 (Box 10, Volume 22)
- Class of 1971 - 25th Reunion Books, 1996 (Box 10, Volume 23)
- Class of 1980, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Class of 1988 - Gift, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)